[
  {

    "front": "George ... was the first president of the United States.",
    "back": "Washington"
  },

  {
    "front": "The Liberty ... is located in Philadelphia?",
    "back": "Bell"
  },
    {
    "front": "The city of ... is capital of New Jersey.",
   "back": "Trenton"
  },
    {
    "front": "The ... lives in the White House.",
    "back": "President"
  },
    {
    "front": "The ... was signed in 1776.",
    "back": "Declaration of Independence"
  },
    {
    "front": "The ... of Liberty was a gift from France",
    "back": "Statue"
  },
    {
    "front": "... was the President of the Confederate States of America",
    "back": "Jefferson Davis"
  },
    {
    "front": "Puerto Rico is considered a ... of the United States.",
    "back": "territory"
  },
    {
    "front": "Ronald Regan was the governor of ..., before becoming President.",
    "back": "California"
  },
    {
    "front": "After years of fighting,... got the right to vote in 1920.",
    "back": "Women"
  },
    {
    "front": "Ben Franklin was one of the only original ... that never served as President",
    "back": "Founding Fathers"
  }

]

